celestreet.com 2018-06-15

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

We at Celestreet are obligated to respect and critically protect the privacy of each and every individual that visits our website or we have dealings with, that provides us with their personal information.

This privacy policy shields all individual information we hold.

**Collection of Information**

Celestreet collect personal information about you as a outcome of and in association with our current business relationship with you. We in general tell you why we are collecting the information from you prior to when we are collecting it. We do not collect sensitive information like sexual preference, health, religious or philosophical beliefs about you. Usually, we collect information directly from you, but sometimes we may acquire list from other sources, from documents in the public domain or from other businesses.

**Information Collected and Use**

We may use or disclose the personal information collected about you in the following ways:

To provide you with relevant Leslie and Claire service or product

To manage the service or product

To perform other organizational responsibilities and functions as well as running our business procedures

To provide information about our services and products that may perhaps be of importance to you

To help in the development of our services and products that may perhaps be of importance to you

To maintain our relationship to you

It may be impossible to deliver services and products to you without the information you provided

**Disclosure of Information**

We do not give any outside organizations access to our client database. We will not sell or disclose personal information to other organizations, for marketing purposes.

We may disclose personal information to service providers who provide services in conjunction with our business (e.g.: agents coordinating conferences, mailing houses, delivery companies), our insurers and organizations through which you choose to make payment to us.

We may release information about you where you have consented to the disclosure, where there is a duty to the public to disclose that information or where we are required to by law.

**Opt Out**

We will make available to you a low cost way of contacting us if you wish to opt out from getting further advertising offers, via email or otherwise. Direct advertising deals will enclose a chance to opt out from getting further communications of this nature.

**Security of Information**

We do not disclose your private personal information but are committed to protecting your privacy and have placed some security measures (electronic and physical) to keep your personal information protected from loss and misuse and unauthorized access, modification and disclosure.We will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for any purpose.

**Access to your Information**

Your information is accessible to you upon your request. But there are occasions where this access may not be deprived under the exemptions contained in the Act and when your access is deprived we will advise you why.

**Quality of Information**

We will take practical measures to ensure that the information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. You are able to contact us and ask for its correction if you feel the information we have about you is inaccurate or incomplete.

**Log Data**

If you visit our website to surf, read, sign into our services, interact with our email notifications our system will log these movements. These website logs are not personally identifiable and we (Celestreet) make no attempt to link them with the individuals who browse the site.

You will provide your username and password when you visit our website to log in to our secure areas to download reports or information. We require you to keep this login and password confidential.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk. We like many other companies do not require cookies for many parts of our services but we use cookies and similar technologies to collect additional website usage data and to improve our services. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookies feature. But you should note that cookies maybe necessary to provide you with features such as merchandise transactions or registered member services.

**Availability of Privacy Policy**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and any revision will be included in the updated policy.

**Privacy Inquiries**

For more inquiries regarding our Privacy Policy contact:

Privacy Personnel

Celestreet  

Lagos State ,Nigeria

Email- [Info@celestreet.com](mailto:Info@celestreet.com)
